Guide to the Montana Attorney General's Office Records 1893-1969
Montana Historical Society Archives
- Subject Files
  - Montana. Adjutant General (includes Butte and Poplar armories), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 28-30)
  - Montana. Agriculture Dept., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 31)
  - Montana. Auditor, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 32)
  - Montana. Beauty and Barber Boards, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 33)
  - Montana. Civil Defense, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 34)
  - Montana. Controller, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 35)
  - Montana. Deaf and Blind, School for, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 64 / 36)
  - Montana. Eastern Montana College, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 1)
  - Montana. Education, Board of, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 2)
  - Montana. Equalization, Board of, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 3)
  - Montana. Examiner, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 4)
  - Montana. Examiners, Board of (includes Advanced Planning), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 5-6)
  - Montana. Fish and Game Dept., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 7)
  - Montana. Forester, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 8)
  - Montana. Governor, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 9)
  - Montana. Health, Board of, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 10)
  - Montana. Highway Commission, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 11)
  - Montana. Highway Patrol, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 12)
  - Montana. Home for Senile Aged (Lewistown), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 13)
  - Montana. Hospital (Warm Springs), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 14)
  - Montana. Industrial Accident Board, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 15)
  - Montana. Industrial School for Boys, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 16)
  - Montana. Labor Dept., 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 17)
  - Montana. Lands and Investments, Dept. of, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 18)
  - Montana. Legislative Council, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 19)
  - Montana. Liquor Control Board, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 20)
  - Montana. Livestock Commission, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 21)
  - Montana. Medical Examiners Board, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 22)
  - Montana. Milk Control Board, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 23)
  - Montana. Motor Vehicles, Registrar of, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 24)
  - Montana. Northern Montana College, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 25)
  - Montana. Oil and Gas Conservation Commission, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 26)
  - Montana. Orphans' Home, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 27)
  - Montana. Plumbing Examiners, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 28)
  - Montana. Prison, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 29)
  - Montana. Public Employees' Retirement System, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 30)
  - Montana. Public Instruction, Dept. of, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 31)
  - Montana. Public Welfare, Dept. of, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 65 / 32)
  - Montana. Railroad Commission, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 1)
  - Montana. School of Mines, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 2)
  - Montana. Secretary of State, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 3)
  - Montana. Soldiers' Home, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 4)
  - Montana. State College (Bozeman), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 5)
  - Montana. State University (Missoula), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 6)
  - Montana. Supreme Court, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 7)
  - Montana. Teachers' Retirement System, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 8)
  - Montana. Trade Commission, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 9)
  - Montana. Training School (Boulder), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 10)
  - Montana. Treasurer, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 11)
  - Montana. Tuberculosis Sanitarium (Galen), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 12)
  - Montana. Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 13)
  - Montana. Vocational School for Girls, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 14)
  - Montana. Water Conservation Board, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 15)
  - Montana. Western Montana College, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 16)
  - Mortgages, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 17)
  - Narcotics, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 18)
  - National Association of Attorneys General, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 19)
  - Nepotism, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 20)
  - Oil and gas matters, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 21)
  - Pardon and parole, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 22)
  - Press releases, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 23)
  - Printing, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 24)
  - Prisoners, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 25)
  - Proposed legislation, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 26)
  - Requests for information: A-Z, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 27-32)
  - Resolutions, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 33)
  - Roads, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 34)
  - Salaries, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 35)
  - Salk vaccine (re polio), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 36)
  - School transportation, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 37)
  - Schools, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 38)
  - Soil conservation, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 39)
  - Stocks, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 40)
  - Taxation, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 66 / 41)
  - Unions (labor), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 67 / 1)
  - Vacation leave, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 67 / 2)
  - Veterans (include bonus), 1959-1960 (Box-folder 67 / 3-4)
  - Vocational rehabilitation, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 67 / 5)
  - Water and water courses, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 67 / 6)
  - Adoption, 1962 (Box-folder 67 / 7)
  - Architecture, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 8)
  - Automobiles, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 9)
  - Banks, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 10)
  - Bonds, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 11)
  - Complaints, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 12-19)
  - Contracts, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 20)
  - Corporations, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 21)
  - County Attorneys: Beaverhead-Yellowstone, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 22-27)
  - County Clerks, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 28)
  - County Commissioners, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 29)
  - County Sheriffs, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 30)
  - County Superintendents of Schools, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 31)
  - County Surveyors, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 32)
  - County Treasurers, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 33)
  - Criminal cases, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 34)
  - Criminal identification, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 67 / 35)
  - Doctors and hospitals, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 1)
  - "Dollars for Democrats", 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 2-4)
  - Elections, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 5-6)
  - Employment, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 7)
  - Escheated estates, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 8)
  - Extradition, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 9)
  - Fire departments, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 10)
  - Forestry, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 11)
  - Gambling, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 12)
  - Indians, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 13)
  - Insurance, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 14-16)
  - Investigation, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 17)
  - Justice of the Peace, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 18)
  - Lands, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 19-20)
  - Law enforcement, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 21)
  - Laws, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 68 / 22-25)
  - Leases, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 1)
  - Licenses, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 2-3)
  - Marriage and divorce, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 4-6)
  - Mines and mining, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 7)
  - Montana. Adjutant General, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 8)
  - Montana. Agriculture Dept., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 9)
  - Montana. Auditor, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 10)
  - Montana. Bank Examiner, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 11-12)
  - Montana. Beauty and Barber Boards, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 13)
  - Montana. Children's Center (orphanage), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 14)
  - Montana. Controller, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 15)
  - Montana. Chiropractors Board, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 16)
  - Montana. Civil Defense, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 17)
  - Montana. Deaf and Blind, School for, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 18)
  - Montana. Eastern Montana College, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 19)
  - Montana. Education, Board of, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 20-21)
  - Montana. Engineer, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 23)
  - Montana. Equalization, Board of, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 24)
  - Montana. Examiners, Board of, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 25)
  - Montana. Fish and Game Dept., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 26)
  - Montana. Governor, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 69 / 27)
  - Montana. Health, Board of, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 1)
  - Montana. Highway Commission, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 2)
  - Montana. Highway Patrol, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 3)
  - Montana. Historical Society, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 4)
  - Montana. Industrial Accident Board, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 5-7)
  - Montana. Industrial School for Boys, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 8)
  - Montana. Labor Dept., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 9)
  - Montana. Lands and Investments, Dept. of, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 10-12)
  - Montana. Legislative Council, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 13)
  - Montana. Liquor Control Board, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 14)
  - Montana. Livestock Commission, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 15)
  - Montana. Medical Examiners Board, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 16)
  - Montana. Milk Control Board, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 17)
  - Montana. Motor Vehicles, Registrar of, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 18)
  - Montana. Northern Montana College, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 19)
  - Montana. Oil and Gas Conservation Commission, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 20)
  - Montana. Old Age Home, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 21)
  - Montana. Prison, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 22-23)
  - Montana. Public Employees' Retirement System, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 24)
  - Montana. Public Instruction, Dept. of, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 25)
  - Montana. Public Welfare, Dept. of, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 26-27)
  - Montana. Railroad Commission, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 28)
  - Montana. School of Mines, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 29)
  - Montana. Secretary of State, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 30)
  - Montana. Soldiers' Home, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 31)
  - Montana. State College (Bozeman), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 32)
  - Montana. State Hospital (Warm Springs), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 70 / 33)
  - Montana. State Training School (Boulder), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 1)
  - Montana. State University (Missoula), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 2)
  - Montana. Supreme Court, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 3)
  - Montana. Teachers' Retirement System, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 4)
  - Montana. Trade Commission, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 5)
  - Montana. Tuberculosis Sanitarium (Galen) (includes hearing), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 6-7)
  - Montana. Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 8)
  - Montana. Vocational School for Girls, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 9)
  - Montana. Water Conservation Board, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 10)
  - Montana. Western Montana College, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 11)
  - Mortgages, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 12)
  - Nepotism, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 13)
  - News releases, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 14)
  - Nurses, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 15)
  - Oil and gas matters, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 16)
  - Oppegaard cattle poisoning, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 17)
  - Pardon and parole, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 18)
  - Personal, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 19-20)
  - Pharmacy, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 21)
  - Politics, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 22)
  - Prisoners, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 23-24)
  - Proposed legislation, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 25)
  - Public utilities, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 26)
  - Requests for information: A-Z, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 71 / 27-32)
  - Requests for opinion, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 1)
  - Roads, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 2)
  - Salaries, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 3)
  - School transportation, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 4)
  - Schools, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 5-9)
  - Soil conservation, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 10)
  - Stocks, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 11)
  - Taxation, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 12-15)
  - Traffic safety, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 16)
  - Unions (labor), 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 17)
  - Vacation leave, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 18)
  - Veterans, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 19)
  - Water, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 72 / 20)
  - Western Attorneys General Conference, 1960-1961 (Box-folder 72 / 21-22)
  - Consumer protection, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 72 / 23)
  - Consumer protection legislation questionnaire, 1964 (Box-folder 72 / 24-27)
  - Consumer protection legislation questionnaire, 1964 (Box-folder 73 / 1-2)
  - Montana. Land Board, 1965, 1967 (Box-folder 73 / 3)
  - Montana. Office of Criminal Investigator, 1965 (Box-folder 73 / 4)
  - "Correspondence to be filed in vault", 1959-1962 (Box-folder 73 / 5)
  - Mailing list of people (probably connected with National Guard, law enforcement, etc.), ca. 1960 (Box-folder 73 / 6)
  - Name index to subject files (cards: includes special section for gambling), 1947-1962 (Box-folder 74-89 /)
- Opinions
  - Index to informal opinions, 1897-1915 (Box-folder 90 / 1)
  - Informal opinions: A-W, 1897-1898 (Box-folder 90 / 2-6)
  - Informal opinions: B-H, 1903-1904 (Box-folder 90 / 7)
  - Informal opinions: A-Y, 1905-1908 (Box-folder 90 / 8-20)
  - Informal opinions: A-Z, 1909-1913 (Box-folder 91 / 1-13)
  - Informal opinions: A-H, 1914 (Box-folder 91 / 14)
  - Informal opinions: J-Y, 1914 (Box-folder 92 / 1-2)
  - Informal opinions: A-W, 1915 (Box-folder 92 / 3-6)
  - Index to formal opinions (by subject, code section, session law), 1955-1968 (Box-folder 93 /)
  - Index to formal opinions (by points argued), 1949-1960 (Box-folder 94 /)
  - Index to formal opinions (by case name), 1949-1960 (Box-folder 95 /)
- Dockets
  - Docket registers #1-9, 1893-1963 (Volume Vol. 1-9)
- Dockets (correspondence and other material re cases)
  - Docket #3, case #279: Will B. Shore vs. Peter W. Nelson (re county reorganization), 1914 (Box-folder 96 / 1)
  - Docket #3, case #349: Montana vs. Harrington, as administrator (re John Galena estate), 1915-1920 (Box-folder 96 / 2)
  - Docket #3, case #526: In the matter of R.O. Lucke (re disbarment), 1912-1919 (Box-folder 96 / 3)
  - Docket #3, case #528: J.E. Leary vs. C.T. Young, et al (re Lincoln County High School bonds), 1918 (Box-folder 96 / 4)
  - Docket #3, case #529: City of Billings vs. Public Service Commission et al., 1918 (Box-folder 96 / 5)
  - Docket #3, case #534: Cove Ditch Company vs. Augusta Allard et al. (re condemnation for right of way in Yellowstone County), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 96 / 6)
  - Docket #3, case #535: Montana, ex rel. S.C. Ford vs. Western Loan and Building Company (re alleged illegal stock issues), 1918 (Box-folder 96 / 7)
  - Docket #3, case #536: Montana vs. Anton Schaffer (re sedition), 1918-1921 (Box-folder 96 / 8)
  - Docket #3, case #550: Montana vs. J.M. Swindlehurst (re murder in Livingston), 1918-1919 (Box-folder 96 / 9)
  - Docket #3, case #551: Montana vs. C.R. Weare (re sedition), 1918 (Box-folder 96 / 10)
  - Docket #3, case #552: In the matter of John A. Griffith (re habeas corpus), 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 11)
  - Docket #3, case #553: Richard S. Nutt vs. Samuel V. Stewart, et al. (re State Board of Land Commissioners; Sidney land), 1918 (Box-folder 96 / 12)
  - Docket #3, case #554: Montana vs. D.F. McGregor (re election fraud in Glasgow), 1918-1920 (Box-folder 96 / 13)
  - Docket #3, case #555: Billings Utility Company vs. Public Service et al., 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 14)
  - Docket #3, case #556: Edward Redwing vs. Hill County (re quieting title), 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 15)
  - Docket #3, case #558: Lyman H. Bennett vs. mary F. Bull (re Madison County schools), 1917-1919 (Box-folder 96 / 16)
  - Docket #3, case #561: Montana vs. A. Guie (re burglary of Northern Pacific Railway office), 1920 (Box-folder 96 / 17)
  - Docket #3, case #563: Valley County grand jury (re McGregor case #554), 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 18)
  - Docket #3, case #569: Montana vs. Peter West, et al (re McGregor case #554), 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 19)
  - Docket #3, case #570: Montana vs. W.B. Shoemaker, et al. (re Valley County grand jury; includes list of potential jurors), 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 20)
  - Docket #3, case #571: J.B. Fullerton vs. J.L. DeHart (re Black Beaver Fur Company illegal transportation of furs), 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 21)
  - Docket #3, case #572: Coast Bridge Company vs. Lincoln County (re faulty bridge construction), 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 22)
  - Docket #3, case #574: Montana vs. Libby Yards Company (re discriminatory price cutting), 1919-1920 (Box-folder 96 / 23)
  - Docket #3, case #576: Montana vs. J.A. McGlynn (re sedition), 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 24)
  - Docket #3, case #578: Montana vs. Walter Vandervoort (re murder in Fallon County), 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 25)
  - Docket #3, case #580: Montana vs. W.K. Smith (re sedition), 1920 (Box-folder 96 / 26)
  - Docket #3, case #582: Montana vs. Keil Brothers Inc. et al. (re price fixing), 1919-1920 (Box-folder 96 / 27)
  - Docket #3, case #584: Montana vs. Chris Wehr (re liquor in Havre), 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 28)
  - Docket #3, case #588: Holter Hardware Company vs. Daniel Boyle, et al. (re Montana Trade Commission), 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 29)
  - Docket #3, case #589: Montana vs. George Francis "Long George" (re horse theft in Hill County), 1919-1920 (Box-folder 96 / 30)
  - Docket #3, case #592: E.L. Rugemar vs. J.L. DeHart et al. (re Gallatin County poaching), 1920-1921 (Box-folder 96 / 31)
  - Docket #3, case #600: Wheatland County vs. E.L. Shoemaker (re condemnation proceedings; delinquent taxes; and R.M. Kelly assault and non-support case), 1919-1920 (Box-folder 96 / 32)
  - Docket #4, case #1: Mary Owens vs. Sidney Miller, Register of State Lands (re purchase of school land), 1920 (Box-folder 96 / 33)
  - Docket #4, case #2: Montana vs. W.L. Eckley (re State Bank of Windham), 1918-1925 (Box-folder 96 / 34)
  - Docket #4, case #3: Great Northern Railway vs. Hill County et al. (re taxation), 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 35)
  - Docket #4, case #4: In the matter of Burt Marsh (re disbarment), 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 36)
  - Docket #4, case #6: Great Northern Railway vs. Flathead County (re taxation), 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 37)
  - Docket #4, case #8: Montana ex rel. William L. Gleason vs. Charles T. Stewart, Secretary of State (re voting precincts), 1919 (Box-folder 96 / 38)
  - Docket #4, case #9: Royal Baking Powder Company vs. Dan J. Donohue et al. (re State Board of Health; accuracy in labelling), 1920 (Box-folder 96 / 39)
  - Docket #4, case #12: Montana vs. Martin Bray (re murder in Butte), 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 40)
  - Docket #4, case #14: Montana vs. Thurman Andrick and Charles E. Foss (re abortion in Hill County) (RESTRICTED), 1920 (Box-folder 96 / 41)
  - Docket #4, case #24: Wood Livestock Company vs. J.H. Burke et al. (re violation of State Livestock Sanitary Board regulations on shipment of sheep), 1920-1922 (Box-folder 96 / 42)
  - Docket #4, case #27: Montana vs. Henry Stein (re liquor in Miles City), 1920-1921 (Box-folder 96 / 44)
  - Docket #4, case #32: Montana ex rel. J.J. Gunther vs. J.C. Timmons (re Sheridan County Commissioner's theft of seed grass), 1918-1922 (Box-folder 96 / 45)
  - Docket #4, case #48: Demarcus Wolfe Estate (re "feebleminded" guardianship), 1918-1922 (Box-folder 96 / 46)
  - Docket #4, case #49: Montana, for the Industrial Accident Fund vs. Monarch Mining and Power Company (Ellison) (re nonpayment of fees), 1920 (Box-folder 96 / 47)
  - Docket #4, case #53: Montana vs. John H. Jenkins (re shooting in Havre), 1920 (Box-folder 96 / 48)
  - Docket #4, case #62: Montana vs. Robert M. Kelly (re "Lazy Husband Law"), 1920 (Box-folder 96 / 49)
  - Docket #4, case #64: Montana and James L. Stillwell vs. Emma Drake (re desert land entry in Chouteau County), 1915-1923 (Box-folder 96 / 50)
  - Docket #4, case #65: Montana and Simeon and Edwin Kindle (re murder in Malta), 1923-1924 (Box-folder 96 / 51)
  - Docket #4, case #65a: Montana vs. Peter Dryer (re state land in Dawson County), 1916-1921 (Box-folder 96 / 52)
  - Docket #4, case #66: Carey Land Act Board vs. N.J. Littlejohn (re Flatwillow Project), 1920 (Box-folder 96 / 53)
  - Docket #4, case #67: Montana ex rel. B.K. O'Grady vs. 20th Judicial District Court (re auditing of claims in Plentywood), 1920 (Box-folder 96 / 54)
  - Docket #4, case #73: Montana ex rel. S.C. Ford vs. P.C. Hicox (re prohibition in Red Lodge), 1920 (Box-folder 96 / 55)
  - Docket #4, case #74: Montana ex rel. W.D. Rankin vs. Joseph M. Dixon and Charles T. Stewart (re treasury notes), 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 56)
  - Docket #4, case #83: Montana ex rel. John T. Bonner vs. Joseph M. Dixon et al. (re university bonds), 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 57)
  - Docket #4, case #84: Montana ex rel. Carl O. Long vs. Charley Clark (re liquor in Big Horn County), 1922 (Box-folder 96 / 58)
  - Docket #4, case #87: Montana ex rel. W.D. Rankin vs. Farmers State Bank of Havre, 1921-1923 (Box-folder 96 / 59)
  - Docket #4, case #91: Gas Products Company vs. W.D. Rankin and D.R. Young (re "carbon black case"), 1921-1922 (Box-folder 96 / 60)
  - Docket #4, case #94: Montana vs. Mona May McCully (re murder in Thompson Falls), 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 61)
  - Docket #4, case #96: Mrs. George A. Warburton vs. Industrial Accident Board, 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 62)
  - Docket #4, case #109: Montana, for Industrial Accident Fund vs. Liverpool Silver Mines Company, 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 63)
  - Docket #4, case #113: Montana, ex rel. W.D. Rankin vs. Frank martin (re Lismas Ferry), 1918-1924 (Box-folder 96 / 64)
  - Docket #4, case #114: Mid-Northern Oil Company vs. J.W. Walker, Treasurer of Montana, et al., 1921-1922 (Box-folder 96 / 65)
  - Docket #4, case #115: Montana vs. Joe Vuckovich, alias Joe Wines (re murder in Missoula), 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 66)
  - Docket #4, case #118: Montana vs. Herschel Carmichael (re murder in Miles City), 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 67)
  - Docket #4, case #119: Somers Lumber Company vs. James W. Walker, Treasurer of Montana, 1921-1925 (Box-folder 96 / 68)
  - Docket #4, case #120: Cottonwood Coal Company vs. James W. Walker, Treasurer of Montana, 1921-1925 (Box-folder 96 / 69)
  - Docket #4, case #126: Montana, ex rel. W.D. Rankin vs. Lion Bonding and Surety Company (re Montana Grain Growers), 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 70)
  - Docket #4, case #129: Mutual Oil Company vs. James W. Walker, Treasurer of Montana, 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 71)
  - Docket #4, case #132: Clarks Fork Land and Cattle Company vs. Sanders County, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 96 / 72)
  - Docket #4, case #133: In matter of Clyde Slagle (re disbarment), 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 73)
  - Docket #4, case #134: Montana, ex rel. John S. Nyquist vs. D.J. Martin (re removal of Scobey sheriff; liquor trade), 1921-1923 (Box-folder 96 / 74)
  - Docket #4, case #139: Montana, ex rel. W.D. Rankin vs. William H. Houston (re Paradise liquor), 1921 (Box-folder 96 / 75)
  - Docket #4, case #140: In the matter of Robert E. O'Keefe (re disbarment), 1922 (Box-folder 96 / 76)
  - Docket #4, case #141: Montana vs. Glenna Martin Bolton (re murder of Treasure County undersheriff Irving Keeler), 1921-1923 (Box-folder 96 / 77)
  - Docket #4, case #142: Montana vs. Joe B. Reagin (re murder of Treasure County undersheriff Irving Keeler), 1922-1923 (Box-folder 96 / 78)
  - Docket #4, case #143: The Frantz Corporation vs. James W. Walker, Treasurer of Montana, 1922 (Box-folder 96 / 79)
  - Docket #4, case #144: Montana vs. John Keel (re murder in Green Back Mining Company bunkhouse, Virginia City), 1921-1922 (Box-folder 96 / 80)
  - Docket #4, case #145: Montana vs. Frank Conley (re conduct of State Prison), 1917-1922 (Box-folder 96 / 83-90)
  - Docket #4, case #145: Montana vs. Frank Conley (re conduct of State Prison), 1921-1922 (Box-folder 97 / 1-18)
  - Docket #4, case #145: Montana vs. Frank Conley (re conduct of State Prison) (includes transcript), 1922 (Box-folder 98 / 1-4)
  - Docket #4, case #145: Montana vs. Frank Conley (re conduct of State Prison) (includes transcript), 1922 (Box-folder 98 / 1-4)
  - Docket #4, case #156: Helena Adjustment Company vs. Legal Tender Consolidated Mines Company, 1921-1922 (Box-folder 98 / 5)
  - Docket #4, case #157: Montana, ex rel. W.D. Rankin vs. Farmers State Bank of Cut Bank, 1924 (Box-folder 98 / 6)